push-analytics.com 2013-06-21

# FearZone.com

FEARZONE.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: September 5, 2007 

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of personally identifiable information we collect online when you access the FearZone.com ("we," "us," or "our") web site located at fearzone.com (the "Web Site"). This Privacy Policy applies and is limited to the treatment of information that is collected via the Web Site. We understand and respect your desire for privacy and will make reasonable efforts to use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing and using the Web Site, you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

INFORMATION COLLECTION

FearZone.com and/or its affiliates are the sole owner(s) of the information collected on fearzone.com. We collect information from our users at several different points on our Web Site. For example, we collect personally identifying information, such as your name, e-mail address, and date of birth, when you register for FearZone.com's newsletter (the "Newsletter"), enter contests, or participate in other interactive online activities throughout the Web Site. As described below, we may use such information to provide Newsletters and other information and services to you, award prizes, or for promotional and marketing purposes. We also collect non-personally identifiable information (such as your IP address or domain) for purposes of site administration and to compile aggregate information about usage of the Web Site. We may combine personal information with such usage information or other information we obtain from other resources.

TELL-A-FRIEND

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. We will send the friend an e-mail in response to your request inviting him/her to visit the Web Site. This information is stored solely for the purpose of sending the e- mail.

PURCHASE OF PRODUCTS

If you purchase a product from the Web Site, information may be collected from you, including your credit card and contact information, for transfer to and use by third party providers of the product. Unless otherwise stated, we do not have any responsibility in connection with such purchase and all transactions and use of any customer information are the sole responsibility of the product provider. Be sure to review the product provider's privacy policy and contact them directly if you have any questions.

SURVEYS AND CONTESTS

From time to time our Web Site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use either session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once a user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on a user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. By showing how and when you use the Web Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not and help in targeting advertisements based on your interests. Cookies also allow us to store the personal preferences that you set during each visit to our site, which in turn allows us to speed up your future activities at our site. The advertisements appearing on the Web Site are delivered to you by a third- party advertising network. In the course of delivering an advertisement to you, the advertising provider may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this site through the use of cookies or similar technology. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers on this site as well. We do not control these cookies, and they are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you have received a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You have the option to reject the Web Site's cookies and still use the Web Site, but you may not be able to access or use some of the features on the Web Site.

LOG FILES

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and report aggregate information to our advertisers, our corporate affiliates or consultants, or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information, nor do we compile session activity reports by IP address.

CLEAR GIFS (WEB BEACONS/WEB BUGS)

We employ or our third party advertising company may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), which help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web Site users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. In addition, we may use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients.

SHARING OF INFORMATION

For the purposes described above and to the extent permitted by law and regulations, we may share your personally identifiable information with our affiliates and other sites operated by and for FearZone.com. We share aggregate information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes. We may also disclose personal information in response to a request by law enforcement personnel, a court order or subpoena, or to protect the integrity of our Web Site if we believe that a user has committed unlawful or otherwise harmful acts. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information in connection with any merger or consolidation with, or sale of substantially all of our assets, to an affiliated entity or third party, provided that such party agrees to comply with our Privacy Policy or you are given a choice if such party would like to use such information in a manner materially different from that disclosed in our Privacy Policy.

NEWSLETTERS

You may register for a periodic FearZone.com newsletter, which we will deliver to the e-mail address that you provide.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

From time to time, we may communicate with you via e-mail to provide services and information in regards to issues relating to your account.

CHOICE/OPT-OUT

If you no longer wish to receive our Newsletter, Dedicated E-mails, and other communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the e-mail newsletter with "UNSUBSCRIBE" (and only "UNSUBSCRIBE") in the subject line or by following the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-mail.

SECURITY

We have taken commercially reasonable measures to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and to make proper use of the information that we collect; however, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide to us.

DELETING PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can request to be removed from our active database by contacting FearZone.com Customer Support at support@fearzone.com and unsubscribing from our Newsletter. If you do so, we will delete your personal information from our active database following our receipt of your cancellation request, unless we determine in our sole discretion that we need to retain that information for a longer period of time to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce this Privacy Policy, or FearZone.com's Terms and Conditions, or for other valid business reasons. Please note that we will not remove your historical usage information from our aggregated files when we delete your user account.

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We may, at our sole discretion, revise this Privacy Policy at any time in a manner consistent with applicable law and regulations. When we revise this Privacy Policy, we will incorporate the revisions into this Privacy Policy and will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this web page. We may also notify you by e-mail of any significant changes. Please check the Web Site periodically for the most current version of our Privacy Policy. By using the Web Site or continuing to receive our Newsletter after we have made any modification or revision to the Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

MINORS

Our Web Site is not directed toward individuals under eighteen years old ("Minors") nor do we knowingly collect information from Minors. Minors should not submit to or post on the Web Site any information.

LINKS

The Web Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web Site.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

THIRD PARTY COOKIES

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@fearzone.com.
